A Guide to the Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Collection, 1856-2019
Shenandoah County Library
- Series X: Audio/Visual Materials
  - 38758101567351 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 28)
    - Yard Sale (1 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.162)
    - Yard Sale (2 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.163)
    - Yard Sale (3 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.164)
    - Yard Sale (4 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.165)
    - Yard Sale (5 of 5), Undated (Sleeve 28.166)
    - Unknown Activities, Undated (Sleeve 28.167)
    - New York Trip (1 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.168)
    - New York Trip (2 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.169)
    - New York Trip (3 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.170)
    - New York Trip (4 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.171)
    - Mt. Hebron Church Trip, Undated (Sleeve 28.172)
    - Caroline Furnace, Undated (Sleeve 28.173)
    - Unidentified Wedding, Undated (Sleeve 28.174)
    - Blessing of Animals, Undated (Sleeve 28.175)
    - Unknown Activity, Undated (Sleeve 28.176)
    - Foot Washing, Undated (Sleeve 28.177)
    - Softball Game, Undated (Sleeve 28.178)
    - Altar Window, Undated (Sleeve 28.179)
    - Advent, Undated (Sleeve 28.180)
    - Communion (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.181)
    - Communion (2 of 2),Undated (Sleeve 28.182)
    - Altar (1 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.183)
    - Altar (2 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.184)
    - Altar (3 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.185)
    - Pastor Murray (1 of 4), Undated (Sleeve 28.186)
    - Pastor Murray (2 of 4),Undated (Sleeve 28.187)
    - Pastor Murray (3 of 4),Undated (Sleeve 28.188)
    - Pastor Murray (4 of 4),Undated (Sleeve 28.189)
    - Easter Cross, Undated (Sleeve 28.190)
    - Banners (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.191)
    - Banners (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.192)
    - Baptismal Font, Undated (Sleeve 28.193)
    - Nursery (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.194)
    - Nursery (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.195)
    - Youth Hike (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.196)
    - Youth Hike (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.197)
    - Bus Trips (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.198)
    - Bus Trips (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.199)
    - Negatives, Undated (Sleeve 28.200)
    - Negatives: Woodstock Watertower, Undated (Sleeve 28.201)
    - Burial Place of Pastor Aubury Bowers, Undated (Sleeve 28.202)
    - Community Farm (1 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.203)
    - Community Farm (2 of 2), Undated (Sleeve 28.204)
    - Christmas Pageant, Undated (Sleeve 28.205)
    - Unidentified Church Events, Undated (Sleeve 28.206)
    - Church (1 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.207)
    - Church (2 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.208)
    - Church (3 of 3), Undated (Sleeve 28.209)
    - 210 “Bible School 2” Unlabeled Photographs (1 of 5) (Sleeve 28.210)
    - 210 “Bible School 2” Unlabeled Photographs (2 of 5) (Sleeve 28.211)
    - 210 “Bible School 2” Unlabeled Photographs (3 of 5) (Sleeve 28.212)
    - 210 “Bible School 2” Unlabeled Photographs (4 of 5) (Sleeve 28.213)
    - 210 “Bible School 2” Unlabeled Photographs (5 of 5) (Sleeve 28.214)